http://www.drdoormat.com/privacy

Dr Doormat
SIGN UP FOR UPDATES ABOUT DR. DOORMAT!
View Cart
$0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Security
The Dr.Doormat web site uses sophisticated, industry-standard security software to keep your personal and credit card information from being compromised
as it travels across the Internet. It's safer to use your credit card over the Internet than it is to use it in a restaurant or department store.
Because we care about the safety of your credit card transaction, our server uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with
Netscape Navigator (versions 2.0 and above), Microsoft Internet Explorer (versions 3.0 and above), and AOL (versions 3.0 and above) so that unauthorized
parties cannot read the information that you send. It's our way of making sure your credit card is safe and secure.
Privacy
This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the privacy policy pertaining to www.drdoormat.com (the "Site"). By using the Site, you are agreeing to the
terms set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement.
For purposes of this Privacy Policy Statement, "Personal Information" means any information by which you can be personally identified,
and includes your name, your address, your telephone number, your e-mail address and the like. The Site collects Personal Information only when you
voluntarily submit such Personal Information to us, such as when placing a product order through the Site, whensigning-up for Product Updates, when
entering a contest, and so on.
The Site does not collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of thirteen, and if you are under thirteen, please give us
parental contact information or exit this site.
For each visitor to the Site, our web servers automatically recognize information regarding the visitor's domain name (or that of the visitor's access provider)
and e-mail address. Regardless of the purpose for which it is submitted, it the policy of The Site to maintain all Personal Information as confidential, and to
use such Personal Information for the following purposes:
for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered (for example, to purchase product, to enter a contest, to comment on our products or Site etc.);
to improve the content, appearance and utility of the Site;
to track our visitors' use of the Site for internal market research or other business purposes; and
to notify our visitors of updates to the Site.
It is the policy of The Site to keep Personal Information only for so long as needed for such purposes. At any time, you may obtain a summary of the Personal
Information on record with The Site which has been collected about you via this Site. Except for Personal Information we need to complete your purchase of products,
you may request at any time that The Site dispose of any or all Personal Information about you. In addition, at any time you may request that The Site correct any
such Personal Information; or that such Personal Information be removed from our marketing databases.
To make any request described above, send an e-mail to debbie@drdoormat.com or write to:
Dr. Doormat, Inc. 11140 Rockville Pike Suite 100, #233 Rockville, MD 20852-3148
When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, address and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.
Requesting To Be Removed From Email Lists
If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, you can let us know one of two ways:
1) Email us at service@drdoormat.com 2) Simply click the unsubscribe link in our promotional email; this is located on the button of the each email.
Consumer Service
M-F 9am-5:30pm ET
The Site reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy Statement at any time.
You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy
Statement will mean that you accept those changes.
